Bye.
I didn't come out of.
Hey everybody!
the light.
Whatever.
yourself.
Thank you.
Never ever.
problem.
was in that view.
All is not
drop my core.
ever confused the car first.
Thank you.
Well, when I drive my body...
Why did you confuse me for my body?
It's mine.
me
down so your bodies are just cars that we
operate and drive around.
the dealership we cost society to set it
to label mine.
yours the Irish oh white
No money down 0% APR.
head strike. We're not forced.
course for the rest of our lives.
but I fail to see the logic or pride.
defining myself.
judge in another by the cars we drive.
of who we truly are.
It's found inside.
Listen, I'm not here to tell you how
science is conclu-
We're all making.
Great than the human species, doesn't
exist.
Whoever his story is.
Ready?
the 15th century.
It has worked perfectly, no.
and I'll hit a leg.
one at hand.
Thank you.
Have a great day.
gave you.
Thank you.
black.
Asian Native American Middle
No.
together.
no longer living in the...
calling human beings.
Ever blind us from seeing a person for who
they are.
instead of saying them from the judge.
Oh, pretty tissue, artificial filters on
it.
When you let an artificial label define
yourself.
that my friend who have chosen smallness
of a greatness and minimized your self,
It moves them all.
living.
So smart.
You can figure out what's there on with
each other.
for who?
So what can we do in the face of all this
madness and cannot what is the solution?
trying to control the mind is like trying
to flex.
Just make it.